Curriculum vitae

Personal Information

NAME Dhimas Ernowo Priambodo

ADDRESS Jl. Ratna Taman Sabila No.8, Jatibening, Bekasi,

Indonesia

PHONE NUMBER +62812 1200 2623

EMAIL dhimasernowo@gmail.com

DATE OF BIRTH 29.04.1990

Personal Profile I'm a hard working, and quick to learn. I have strong

problem-solving skills and eager to improve my communication and professional IT skills. As an iOS engineer with two years experience of building whole mobile apps from scratch, I can work unsupervised

alone efficiently or as a member of a team.

Formal Education

DATES 2008 - 2012

QUALIFICATION AWARDED Bachelor of Computer

PRINCIPAL STUDIES Informatics

INSTITUTION Diponegoro University Semarang

GPA 3.46

PUBLICATION Engineering Online Music Store Application Using In-

App Purchase Server Product Model on iPad iOS Based

Mobile Device

Non-Formal Education 2014 - present, EF English Center for Adults

Work Experience

DATES February 2013 - present

POSITION iOS Research & Development Engineer

RESPONSIBILITIES - Lead and build iOS project, mostly for company-

product projects

- Analyse requirements given by user and give user a brief explanation about the program user's actually

wanted

- Design the database, data structure, and web service

- Research for new iOS and Mac OS Technology

Curriculum vitae

- Take part to kick-off meeting, to offer company

service to client

EMPLOYER / ADDRESS PT. Enervolution / Jl. Senopati No. 74, Kebayoran Baru,

Jakarta

DATES July 2011 - December 2011

POSITION Self Employment

RESPONSIBILITIES Build a web-based asset management system in

Semarang using ASP.NET

EMPLOYER / ADDRESS PT. Vermindo Technology Utama / Jl. Stonen Timur IV.

1A, Semarang

DATES May 2010 - March 2011

POSITION Internship

RESPONSIBILITIES Build a school management information system,

SHICHIDA, Australia

EMPLOYER / ADDRESS PT. Cell Box Indonesia / Jl. Pulau Bira Raya A8/4, Jakarta

Skills and Competences

LANGUAGE SPOKENBahasa Indonesia (Native) **OTHER LANGUAGE(S)**English (Intermediate)

ACHIEVEMENTS 2006 Science National Olympiad for Computer Science

SKILLS Willingness, Team Work as well as Individual Work,

Problem Solver, Attention to Detail